Guide to the Student Action With Farmworkers records, 1950-2020, bulk 1992-2016 RL.01128
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Printed Material, 1978-2016 and undated; 14 boxes
  Arranged by title; most pieces are individually foldered but there are also collections of similar materials grouped in folders with general titles.
  Additional print materials are found in the Administrative Files series, where there are resource files and print materials related to events, protests, teaching, and organizations. Some are also found in the Ephemera series.
  Arrangement
  Arranged in four subseries: SAF Publications and Resource Binders; Non-SAF Publications; Theses; and Children's Books. Most of the subseries materials are arranged alphabetically in title order.
  - SAF Publications and Resource Binders, 1988-2015 and undated
    Contains printed material produced by Student Action with Farmworkers and some by other allies, most of which were housed by SAF in folders and binders and arranged chronologically.
    Materials cover a wide range of issues related to migrant farmworkers, and there are resource files containing listings and indexes for health, legal, service learning service, and educational issues.
    - Migrant and Seasonal Farmworkers in NC, 1988, 2 folders (Box 71)
    - SAF (Student Action with Farmworkers) publication, 1990-1995 (Box 102)
    - Miscellaneous farm material, 1992 (Box 71)
    - From the Ground Up, 1993 July-1998 Fall (Box 145)
    - From the Ground Up, Fall/Winter, 1999 (Box 101)
    - Presentation information, 1994 (Box 71)
    - SAF Intern Referral Service Directory, 1994 (Box 145)
    - Photographic postcards of farmworker and children and Mexican music band, by: Chris Johnson, intern (2 copies of each image), circa 1997; 4 items (Box 145)
    - Stop! Child Labor, 1996 (Box 71)
    - SAF publications, 1996-2000 (2 folders) (Box 103)
    - Camp health aide manual, 1997, 4 folders (Box 71)
    - NC: Farmworkers Services Coordinating Committee, 1997, 3 folders (Box 71)
    - Into the Fields, Mobilizing Students to Work with Farmworkers on Campuses and in Communities, 1997; 2 copies (Box 145)
    - College Choice Guide for Migrant Students and Parents, 1998 and undated; 2 folders, 2 copies (Box 145)
    - Fields without Borders, 1998; 2 copies (Box 145)
    - Living the American Dream, 1998 (Box 145)
      Print-out version.
    - SAF fliers, pamphlets, brochures file, 1998-2015 (Box 145)
      Color publicity about SAF programs such as Levante, and events such as the Sowing Seeds for Change symposium. Includes some factsheets and boycott information.
    - SC Migrant Health Program: 1998 Outreach Worker Orientation, 2 folders (Box 71)
    - Farmworker Folklife, 1999 (Box 145)
    - From the Ground Up, 1999 Spring-2002 Summer (Box 145)
    - Como empezar un Club AIM: Un manual de acción estudiantil con trabajadores agrícolas / How to start an Aim Club, 2000 (Box 146)
    - College Choices Guide for Migrant Students and Parents, 2000 (Box 146)
    - Recollections of Home, 2000; 2 copies (Box 146)
    - College Choices Guide for Migrant Students and Parents, 2001 (Box 146)
    - Cultured Ground: A Compilation of Folklife Documentaries by SAF interns, 2001 (Box 146)
    - Legal Immigration Forum, 2001 March, 2 folders (Box 71)
    - Publications, 2001-2004; 1-2 of 12 folders (Box 71)
    - Publications, 2001-2004; 3-12 of 12 folders (Box 72)
    - SAF: Solidarity Since 1992, 2002; 2 copies (Box 146)
    - From the Ground Up, 2002 Fall/Winter-2006 Winter (Box 146)
    - Publications, 2005; 6 folders (Box 72)
    - Publications, 2006; 5 folders (Box 72)
    - From the Ground Up, 2006 Summer-2011 Winter (Box 146)
    - SAF 15 Year Anniversary celebration event flier, 2007 (Box 146)
      Event pamphlet.
    - NC Farmworker Institute information sheet, 2007-2008; 2 items (Box 146)
    - Publications, 2007; 3 folders (Box 73)
    - Publications, 2008; 4 folders (Box 73)
    - Publications, 2009; 3 folders (Box 73)
    - Publications, 2010 (Box 115)
      Compilation of newspaper clippings and SAF publications
    - Publications, 2011 (Box 115)
      Compilation of newspaper clippings, journals, and SAF publications
    - Publications, 2012; 2 folders (Box 115)
    - Student Action with Farmworkers: 20 Years of Growing Farmworker Activists / Estudiantes en acción con campesinos: 20 años de fomentar el activismo a favor de trabajadores agrícolas, 2012 (Box 146)
    - Theater in the Fields: A Guide for Dynamic Outreach with Farmworkers / Teatro en el campo: Un manual para encuentros dinámicos con campesinos, 2012 (Box 146)
    - Compilation of health materials, undated, 6 folders (Box 73)
    - Newcomer Arts: A Strategy for Successful Integration, undated, 2 folders (Box 73)
    - A Resource Guide to Scholarships for Hispanic and Migrant Students, undated (Box 146)
    - SAF Dismantling Oppression: Philosophy and Roles, undated (Box 146)
      "From the Peace Development Fund racism workbook"
    - SAF informational fliers, undated (2 copies of each) (Box 146)
  - Theses and Student Papers, 1991-2007
    Contains masters theses and student papers related to farmworkers and migrant workers, many specifically focusing on North Carolina. Topics include workers rights, education, identity, and women's labor. Arranged chronologically.
    - Corrie, Carolyn. 'And Justice for All?' The Migrant Farmworker Crisis and the Failure of Liberal Reform, 1991. (Box 74)
    - Callahan, Cathy. Stranded, Uprooted and Voiceless: Latin American Farmworking Women in NC, 1992. (Box 74)
    - Mosher, Kathleen C. Delicate Art, Low Pay: The Legacy of Crab Pickers in NC, 1993. (Box 74)
    - Hickle, Andrea. Focus Groups, Interviews, and Lay Health Advisor training with Mexican Migrant Farmworkers, 1996. (Box 74)
    - Ludwig, Erik K. First Class Education and 'Second Hand' Workers, 1998 April. (Box 74)
    - Bagby, Joe. Sweat Inequality: The Social Alienation of Mexican Migrant Farmworkers in NC, 2000. (Box 74)
    - Payne, Brian. Taking Back the Reins of Identity Transformation, 2000. (Box 74)
    - Rhodes, Catherine R. Modern-Day Slavery: the Involuntary Servitude of NC's H-2A Farmworkers Today, 2000. (Box 74)
    - Abernathy, Lee E. Education of a Gringa: Encounters with Mexicans in the US, 2001. (Box 74)
    - Sugg, Jennifer H. ESL and the Education of Latino Students in Lee County of NC, 2001. (Box 74)
    - Etienne, Stephanie. Provider Knowledge of Farmworker Agricultural Chemical Exposure, 2004. (Box 74)
    - Student papers, 6 folders (Box 75)
    - Wilson, Julie. Diversity in Solidarity: Student Action with Farmworkers' Archive of Intern Writing, 2007. (Box 94)
    - Wilson, Julie. Diversity in Solidarity: Student Action with Farmworkers' Archive of Intern Writing, 2007 (Box 146)
  - Non-SAF Publications, 1978-2016 and undated
    Contains publications such as serials, newspapers, pamphlets, booklets, reports, and fliers related to migrant workers, farmworkers, and activism. Many are grassroots, community-based publications with a focus on North Carolina. Arranged alphabetically by title.
    - Action, Inspiration, Motivation: Randolph County AIM Club Members Share their Experiences, 2001 (Box 76)
    - Action, Inspiration, Motivation: Randolph County AIM Club Members Share Their Experiences, Spring 2001 (Box 101)
    - Articles, 1988-2000, 2 folders (Box 101)
    - Association of Farmworker Opportunity Programs, "America's Farmworker Children: Harvest of Broken Dreams" and "Children at Work", 2009 and 2011 (Box 76)
    - Bachpan Bachao Andolan promotional material [children's rights and protection group based in India, founded 1980], after 1980 (Box 101)
    - Blessing the hands: Farm worker issues in a biblical context. A curriculum on farm workers for faith communities, participant booklet (National Farm Worker Ministry), 2005 (Box 76)
    - Boycott Grapes, United Farm Workers of America, AFL-CIO 25th anniversary, 1987 (Box 76)
      United Farm Workers of America, AFL-CIO
    - Campus outreach, the journal of student community involvement: rural communities, the lost realm of service (Campus Outreach Community League), 1993; 2 copies (Box 76)
    - The Catalyst, Sisters of Charity Foundation, South Carolina: special edition on migrant farmworker services, after 2003 (Box 76)
    - Children in the Fields: An American Problem (Assoc. of Farm Worker Opportunity Programs), 2007 (Box 76)
    - Close to Slavery: Guest Worker Programs in the U.S., Southern Poverty Law Center, 2007 (Box 76)
    - Common Ground: A publication for the N.C. Center for Nonprofits newsletters, Summer 2012-Fall 2013 (Box 101)
    - Communities Against Sweatshops, campaign kits in four folders, 2000 (Box 76)
    - Community Change, Duke University Community Services Center, Spring 1996 (Box 76)
    - Community News, NC Justice and Community Development Center, Spring 2004 (Box 76)
    - Conflict Management, 2004 (Box 76)
    - 19th Constitutional Convention, United Farm Workers, 2012 (Box 76)
    - The Cost of Your Shirt, 1997 (Box 76)
    - Crossroads, NC Humanities Council, Fall 2007 (Box 76)
    - Cuban/Haitian Entrant Program, Interpreter/Translator Directory, 1982 Summer (Box 76)
    - CUSLAR Newsletter, Committee on U.S./Latin American Relations, Ithaca NY, 2013-2014 (Box 76)
    - Danger Under the Sun: Protect Yourself - Drink Water!, 2001 August (Box 76)
    - Derechos laborales para trabajadores contratados bajo el programa H-2A en Carolina del Norte, Legal Aid NC, 2009 (Box 76)
    - Directory, National Farmworker Ministry, 1998 (Box 76)
    - Divinity: Duke University, 2003 Winter; 2 copies (Box 76)
    - Documentar la accion comunitaria: Guía para comunidades, artistas y activistas, Center for Documentary Studies, 2001 (Box 76)
    - Doña Genoveva: Manos que brindan salud, photo narrative of NC migrant healer, for Rural Women's Health Project in partnership with SAF and CDS, 2003; 2 copies (Box 76)
      "En el noreste de Carolina del Norte, vive Doña Genoveva Camacho, una campesina nacida en San Roque, Guanajuato, México. Ella es una Señora que sabe curar."
    - Duke: A Magazine for Alumni and Friends, View into a different world, article on SAF's Into the Fields project, 1991 June-July (Box 76)
    - Duke: A Magazine for Alumni and Friends, 2012 (Box 101)
    - East Coast Migrant Stream Forum, 2005 and 2006 (Box 77)
    - "El terror invisible" Spanish-language pamphlet on pesticide safety published by PACE (Preventing Agricultural Chemical Exposure), 2000 (Box 77)
    - Emerging Photographer, the Documentary Issue, 2011 (Box 77)
    - "Encountering Law Enforcement" SAF resource file, 1998-2010 and undated (Box 77)
      Four booklets: La lucha contra los abusos de la policia (ACLU); Lo que todo el mundo debe saber sobre la violencia en el hogar (NC Victim Assistance Network); Picked up: Guía para imigrantes detenidos en Carolina del Norte (NC Justice Ctr); Know your rights when encountering law enforcement (ACLU).
    - False Profits: Who Wins, Who Loses when the IMF, World Banks, and WTO Come to Town, 2000 (Box 77)
    - Secret, Mosi Farm Team The Independent, 2007 Aug. 15 (Box 77)
    - Farmworker Justice annual report and 25th anniversary publication, 2006 (Box 77)
    - Farmworker Justice Fund, 2005 (Box 77)
    - Fast for Life!, July 16-Ugust 21, Delano, CA, large UFW booklet with 2-page Cesar Chavez statement and testimonials and ads by supporters, 1988 (Box 77)
    - FLOC...In the Community: FLOC NC Summer Organizing Report, 2003 (Box 77)
      Illustrated with photos of substandard versus improved FLOC farmworker housing.
    - Food and Justice, United Farm Workers (UFW) publication (11 issues), 1985-1988 (Box 77)
    - From Cambodia to Greensboro, 2004 (Box 77)
    - From Orchards to the Internet: Confronting Contingent Work Abuse, 2002 (Box 77)
    - Georgetown Journal on Poverty and Law Policy, The Environment and Social Injustice of Farmworker Pesticide Exposure, Spring, 2012 (Box 101)
    - Globalization in our Front Yard, 2000 (Box 77)
    - Gracias por los campesinos calendar by Celia Roberts (Colorado) and SAF staff/interns, 2008 (Oversize-box 147)
    - Grassroots Fundraising Journal, Nov./Dec. 2011-July/Aug. 2013 (Box 101)
    - The Guestworker, 2005 (Box 77)
    - Guestworkers and Enganchadores: Changing Labor Relations in U.S. Rural Communities, Powerpoint printout from talk by author David Griffith, circa 2007 (Box 77)
    - Harvesting the Harvesters, Migrant Educators' National Training OutReach, training manuals for migrant educators, 1985; Series of 10 training manuals on different topics, intended as a correspodence course for migrant educators. (Box 77)
    - Health Outreach Partners, collection of outreach strategies from the field, undated (Box 101)
    - Highlander Research and Education Center Strategic Assessment and Action, 2013 (Box 77)
    - The Human Cost of Food, book cover proof, published 2002 (Oversize-box 147)
    - Immigrants in Our Own Land and Selected Early Poems by Jimmy Santiago Baca, 1990 (Box 77)
    - Increasing Access to Food and Nutrition for Migrant Children, 2006 (Box 77)
    - Independent Weekly, 1999 Feb. and 2007 Aug. (Box 101)
    - Injustice for All: The Rise of the U.S. Immigration Policing Regime, National Network for Immigrant and Refugee Rights, 2010 Dec. (Box 102)
    - Innovative Outreach Practices Report, 2005 (Box 77)
    - Innovative Outreach Practices Report, 2011 (Box 77)
    - Inside Agromedicine newsletters, Summer 2011-Winter 2014 (Box 101)
    - International Labor Office/Organization publications, 2005-2011 (Box 101)
    - Into the Fields: A Report on Migrant and Seasonal Farmworkers in MN, 1995 Oct (Box 77)
    - Into the Fields: A Guide and Resource Manual for Student Initiatives with Farmworkers, by Carolyn Corrie, Center for Documentary Studies, 1991 (Box 78)
      Two copies of a 127-page manual for the pilot program "Into the Fields," which led to the formation of the organization Student Action with Farmworkers. Includes preface by Robert Coles and testimonials from college students working in similar programs.
    - Juntos con nuestra herencia: entrevistas, poesías e historias orales de la comunidad latina en Durham, Center for Documentary Studies, 1999 (Box 78)
    - La Voz de Carolina, 1996 June 30 (Box 78)
    - La Voz de Carolina, 1996 July 31 (Box 78)
    - La Voz Independiente, 2011 Feb. 3 (Box 101)
    - Latino Studies, Latino/as in the Media, Vol. 9, Number 2-3, Summer/Autumn, 2011 (Box 101)
      Special issue.
    - L & S Link: Learn and Serve America: Higher Education Training and Technical Assistance Newsletter, 1995 November; 2 copies (Box 78)
    - Learning about Green Tobacco Sickness: Juan's Experience / Aprenda sobre la enfermedad del tabaco verde: la experiencia de Juan, a photonovel produced by Sara Quandt and Thomas Arcury, Wake Forest School of Medicine, 2001 (Box 78)
    - Leo Cuellar Says: Work Smart... Work Safely... With Farm Chemicals (bilingual), 1980s (Box 78)
      Safety pamphlet endorsed by soccer star Leo Cuellar.
    - Life as we see it / Como vemos la vida, by Center for Documentary Studies, Juntos con Nuestra Herencia program, 1999 (Box 78)
    - Life's Learning: Education with Three Mexican Families in NC, 1991 (Box 78)
    - Living the American Dream: Economic Justice for Farmworkers, 1998; 2 copies (Box 78)
      Bound version.
    - Maps of Farmworker Camps in NC, 1988 Summer (Box 78)
    - Media Guide to Covering Farmworkers in NC, 2001 (Box 78)
    - Memories of Carolinian immigrants: Autobiographies, diaries, and letters from colonial times to the present, by Andreas Lixl [partial typed manuscript], 2006 August (Box 78)
      Typescript draft of book, containing 308 pages out of 359 total. Includes section on Seira Reyes, an artist and SAF intern whose work is in this SAF collection.
    - Mexico Infopak, after 1992 (Box 78)
    - Mezcla: A Bilingual Student Magazine, 2014-2015 Winter (Box 78)
      Contains an article, "Los campesinos," by Luis Acosta with photos by Devereaux Swaim, SAF students/interns
    - Migrant Summer: A documentary view of the lives of migrant farmworkers in North Carolina, by Duke University students through the Center for Documentary Studies, 1991 (Box 78)
      Student names: Sarah Carroll; Carolyn Corrie; Mike Evans; Lisa Hazirjian; Evie Kim; Eric Martin; Anna Snowdon; David Thomas; Sylvia Thompson; Luisa Tio; Jorge Vigil; Stephanie Wagner; Jeff Whetstone; Lane Windham.
      Binding is separated - handle with care.
    - Miscellaneous newsletters, 2011-2012 (Box 101)
    - NC Raise UP pamphlet for living wage campaign (Carolina Workers Organizing Committee), circa 2014 (Box 78)
    - Miscellaneous print publications, 1993-2012 and undated (Box 102)
    - Neighborhood Voices: New Immigrants in Northeast Central Durham / Voces del barrio, nuevos inmigrantes en noreste central de Durham, by Jill Hemming, 2001 (Box 78)
    - National Committee for Responsive Philanthropy, Strengthening Democracy, Increasing Opportunities: Impacts of Advocacy, Organizing, and Civic Engagement in the Gulf/Midsouth Region, undated (Box 102)
    - National Committee for Responsive Philanthropy quarterly journal, Spring 2011-Winter 2014 (Box 102)
    - National Farmworker Ministry News and Views, Spring 2011-Summer 2014 (Box 102)
    - Network News Catholic Migrant Farmworker Network, 2009 Spring (Box 78)
    - Network News, Catholic Migrant Farmworker Network newsletters, Volume 22, Numbers 1 and 2, Autumn-Winter, 2012-Spring 2014 (Box 102)
    - Network News, National Network for Immigrant and Refugee Rights, 2005 Spring (Box 78)
    - New Solutions: A Journal of Environmental and Occupational Health Policy, Volume 22, Number 2, 2012 (Box 102)
    - NC Crossroads, NC Humanities Council, special issue with writings and interview with Latino immigrants in NC, 1998 September-October (Box 79)
    - NC Crossroads, NC Humanities Council, special issue on Latino teenagers in transition, 2003 May (Box 79)
      Contains section on teen artist and SAF intern Seira Reyes.
    - NC Farm Labor Rules and Regulations, 1991 (Box 79)
    - North Carolina farm workers fact sheets, by the NC Farmworker Institute, 2007, 2009 (Box 79)
      Four fact sheets on the history of farmworker immigration, health and safety, demographics, and labor statistics.
    - North Carolina Crossroads, NC Humanities Council, 1996 Spring and 2002 Spring (Box 79)
      Two issues with grant funding entries for SAF as well as textual entries about Into the Fields and Jill Hemming's work on immigrants in Northeast Durham, NC.
    - North Carolina Justice Center, 2011 (Box 102)
    - North Carolina Medical Journal, Volume 72, Number 6, 2011 Nov.-Dec. (Box 102)
    - North Carolina Migrant Housing and Safety Standards: An Empirical Assessment of Compliance and Enforcement Statistics, Ellen Phelps, 2006 (Box 79)
    - NCSU Alumni Magazine, 1995 Fall (Box 79)
      Alumni Magazine.
    - Not Yo Mama's Home Cookin': The Changing Faces of Rural North Carolina, 2006 (Box 79)
      "A compilation of rural teen perspectives, A Hidden Voicees Project, Cedar Grove, NC." Partners included SAF. Illustrated with many photographs.
    - Office of Research Integrity newsletter, 2011 Mar. and Sep. (Box 102)
    - Organización Internacional del Trabajo publications, 2012 and undated (Box 102)
    - The Other Immigrants, 2005 (Box 79)
    - Pesticide Detection, 1988 (Box 79)
    - Photo Blitz, Guilford College poster listing exhibit "Fields without borders," photos by SAF interns, 1999 (Box 79)
    - Portales / Gateways, exhibit guide on Hispanic/Latinx migrations, Smithsonian Anacostia Community Museum (2016-2017), 2 copies (Box 79)
    - Poverty and Race Research Action Council newsletters, 2011 May/June-2014 July/Aug. (Box 102)
    - Predictors of Incidence and Prevalence of Green Tobacco Sickness among Latino Farmworkers in NC, 2000; 2 copies (Box 79)
      28-page draft report of forthcoming article for the Journal of Epidemiology and Community Health; includes copies of two related journal articles.
    - The Prism, 1996 Nov. (Box 79)
    - A Profile of Demographic, Occupational, and Health-Related Characteristics of The Migrant and Settled (Seasonal) Hired Farmworker Population of Florida, by Martha I. Arrieta, Frances J. Walker, and Thomas J. Mason, 1998 (Box 79)
    - La promesa en el derecho / The Promise in the Law, Hispanic National Bar Association, circa 2015 (Box 101)
    - Puentes, "Publicación informativa y literaria del Center for Public Service, Gettysburg College y la comunidad Latina en el condado de Adams, Pennsylvania", 1996 December and 1997 March (Box 79)
      Two issues of newsletter.
    - Pushing Back: Women Workers Speak Out on Free Trad e, Women United for Worker Justice (STITCH), 2004, Aug. (Box 102)
    - Reflections of a Former Migrant, Horace A. Judson, Morgan State College, Maryland, keynote address to Migrant Education Institute, June 1976, 1978 (Box 79)
      Includes many photographs of migrant children and others.
    - Report on Latino Culture and Traditional Arts in Tennessee, prepared for the Tennessee Arts Commission, by Norma E. Cantú, 1999 November (Box 79)
      59-page report with bibliography and appendices.
    - Salud! Health and Safety Programs, 2012 Jan.-Nov. (Box 102)
    - The Service Learning Educator: A Guide to Program Management, by the National Center for Service Learning, 1980 (Box 79)
      101-page manual.
    - Siembra: A Newsletter for Farmworker Friends and Advocates, Fall 2011-Summer 2014 (Box 103)
    - Conversaciones del alma: Luis Rodrigues en Carolina del Norte / Soul Talk: Luis Rodriguez in North Carolina, published by the NC Literary Consortium, 2001; 2 copies (Box 94)
    - Stone Circles: Sustaining activists and strengthening the work for justice through spiritual practices and principles, brochure from organization, 2003 (Box 94)
    - Struggle for Justice, A Tribute to Cesar Chavez, program brochure from Smithsonian National Museum of American History, 1993 (Box 94)
    - Student Intern Perspectives, U-Migrant Project, a Final Project by U-Migrant Project Student Interns, 1996 (Box 94)
    - Tallando Tradiciones: Preservando la cultura mexicana, photo-narrative by Rural Women's Health Project, 2003; 2 copies (Box 94)
    - Testimonies from the Fields: Clergy, Community Activists, Students and Members of Labor Unions Report on the Oregon Farmworkers' Struggle for Justice, 1997 (Box 94)
    - Tobacco Road, Duke undergraduate publication, special issue on activism at Duke, 1995 April; 2 copies (Box 94)
    - To Be Rather than to Seem: Reflections on Race in NC, Z. Smith Reynolds Foundation annual report, 2001 (Box 94)
    - Towerview, with article, "Food with Dignity," on NC farmworkers by Christina Peña, March 2012 (Box 94)
    - UMOS (United Migrant Opportunity Services) annual report, 2010-2011 (Box 103)
    - Uprooting Injustice / Arracando de Raiz la Injusticia: A Report on Working Conditions for NC Farmworkers and the Farm Labor Organizing Committee's Mt. Olive Initiative, Institute for Southern Studies, 1999 March and July (Box 94)
      Two issues
    - Urban Latino, magazine with article by Lisa Reyes on farmworkers, 2001 Apr./May (Box 94)
    - Various event invitations and postcard flyers, 1998-2014 and undated (Box 94)
    - Various publications and writings of Hector Neri, 1998-2003 (Box 94)
      Also includes correspondence about the writings included.
    - The Voice of Farmworkers: A Journal to Commemorate Farmworker Advocacy Day 2000, Albany, New York (Box 94)
    - Volunteer 101: News 2 Educate + Activate College Volunteers, 1998 Fall; 2 copies (Box 94)
    - Where Destiny Takes Me: Story of a Salvadoran Exile, American Friends Service Committee, 1991 May (Box 94)